[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Car accident victim Victor Pascow is one of the characters in this 1989 horror film directed by Mary Lambert.", "correct_answer": "Pet Sematary", "incorrect_answers": ["Undead", "Sugar Hill", "The Serpent and the Rainbow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of glands are the Glands of Montgomery?", "correct_answer": "Sebaceous glands", "incorrect_answers": ["Lacrimal glands", "Sudoriferous glands", "Salivary glands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The gowni is a typical national costume in which African country?", "correct_answer": "Tanzania", "incorrect_answers": ["Malawi", "Uganda", "Indonesia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2001 Spanish movie Y Tu Mama Tambien translates into what?", "correct_answer": "And Your Mother Too", "incorrect_answers": ["You and Your Mother", "Mother Too", "Mom and Me"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the missing number in the following sequence: 10, 20, 100, ___, 280, 560, 640.", "correct_answer": "200", "incorrect_answers": ["110", "180", "270"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the historic attack on Normandy on June 6, 1944, which was part of World War II military operations of the Allied Powers against Nazi Germany?", "correct_answer": "Operation Neptune", "incorrect_answers": ["Operation Overlord", "Operation  Belgrani", "Operation Barbarosa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did reconstructive and plastic surgery originate?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["Roman Empire", "Ancient Greece", "Egypt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was ejected from the first Star Destroyer in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correct_answer": "Imperial Probe Droid", "incorrect_answers": ["Nothing", "Tie Fighter", "Transport Pod"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the the following is not a step in the brewing of beer?", "correct_answer": "steeping", "incorrect_answers": ["sparging", "mashing", "boiling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Santorini volcanic islands are part of what European country?", "correct_answer": "Greece", "incorrect_answers": ["Denmark", "Spain", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who thought of the name iPod?", "correct_answer": "Vinnie Chieco", "incorrect_answers": ["Jonathan Ive", "Tony Fadell", "Steve Jobs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fiberfill is used to make ski jackets. What can be recycled to make enough Fiberfill for one ski jacket?", "correct_answer": "5 plastic soda bottles", "incorrect_answers": ["384 pounds of newspaper", "1045 styrene cups", "149 pounds of composted lawn material"]}]